herdprotect.com 2018-12-18

# Privacy Policy - herdProtect

Reason Software Company Inc., is the provider of the herdProtect software (the “Software”), and the website http://www.herdprotect.com/ (the “Website”), understands the importance of protecting personal information. This privacy policy outlines how Reason Software collects, uses, and discloses your personal information. 

### What information do we collect from the Website and how is it used?

What information do we collect from the Website and how is it used?

When using and accessing our Website, we may use and collect information of technical nature, including your IP address, activity log of your use of the Website, user agent, information about your browser. We use this information to better understand your needs, provide you with the services you have requested, and with a view to provide you with better service. We also use the information to operate our services, and to support internal operations such as support, security, debugging, and reporting and analytics.

Cookies. We use technologies like cookies and pixel tags to provide, improve, protect and promote the Website. For example, cookies help us with things like understanding how you are interacting with our Website, and improving them based on that information. You can set your browser to not accept cookies, but this may limit your ability to use the Website.

We may further use your information to connect social media accounts which you have actively linked with our Services (such as Facebook or StumbleUpOn, Twitter, or Pinterest).

### What information does the Software collect and how is it used?

Reason Software gathers information in order to provide the products, service, and support that are part of the Software. 

We collect a unique id that we generate and your IP address. We also collect basic information about your device, such as operating system details, default browser, and device manufacturer.

Reason Software uses your information to better understand your needs, provide you with the services you have requested, and with a view to provide you with better service. We also use the information to operate our services, and to support internal operations such as support, security, debugging, and reporting and analytics. We use your information to help you complete a transaction, (including fulfillment of orders and promotional offers), to communicate back to you, to inform you of and update you on services and benefits, and to manage and renew your subscription(s). Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing, maintenance of your subscription, and fraud protection and are not used for other purposes without your permission.

Reason Software will keep your information for as long as you are user of our product(s) and thereafter, for no longer than is reasonably necessary for internal reporting and reconciliation purposes and to provide you with any feedback or information that you might request or require.

### About or advertising policies

We utilize thrid party vendors such as Google to provide advertising on our site. These vendors, including Google and Facebook, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits. Google's and Facebook’s use of cookies enables them and their partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to our web site and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick and facebook cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting the ads preference manager and http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2. You may also visit aboutads.info to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising.

### Does Reason Software disclose personal information?

In limited circumstances, Reason Software may need to share your information in order to meet your particular needs. Reason Software has a number of relationships with vendors with whom we may share your personal information for the purpose of providing a service, fulfilling an order, or meeting your other needs. For example, we use selected vendors for the purpose of providing credit card transaction processing services. These vendors verify your purchase information, such as credit card number, and authorize your transaction. In doing so, the vendors have access to limited information about users, but they are prohibited from using the information for any other purpose. Reason Software imposes strict confidentiality obligations on all third-party vendors with whom we share your information. By providing your information to us, you are deemed to consent to the transfer of your information to our third-party vendors in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

We may also need to share your personal information with our corporate affiliates to support our internal operations as listed above. From time to time, Reason Software may provide personal information to law enforcement authorities or other third parties in response to a subpoena, an official inquiry, or as may be required in the case of national security. 

### Children

Reason Software does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13, except as permitted by the US Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. If we learn we have collected personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that data from our systems.

### Additional information for users in the European Economic Area, United Kingdom, or Switzerland

If you are located in the European Economic Area, United Kingdom, or Switzerland, the following provisions apply to you:

  1. We act as a controller and processes personal data as necessary for the performance of the contract with you. Accordingly, we will process your personal data as necessary to operate the Software, and to reply to your queries.
  2. We also process personal data as necessary for our legitimate interests to provide you with the Website in a proper and secure manner. 
  3. We may also process for marketing purposes based on our legitimate interest to provide you with information on our products and services.
  4. Reason Software may process your information for compliance with applicable legal obligations.
  5. Data subject rights (Software) - Please note that you have the right to request from Reason Software access to and rectification or erasure of your personal data it processes as controller, or to restrict or to object to processing of your personal data in accordance with the provisions of the GDPR. In order to submit a request for accessing and/or deleting your information, please submit a request to our support through the following email, deleteme@builtwithreason.com. Please note that Reason Software will process your request subject to verification of your identity.
  6. We will transfer your information to the United States based on the Standard Contractual Clauses. If you wish to receive a copy of these clauses, please contact us through the below contact details.
  7. Data subject rights (Website) – As we collect the minimum information necessary for the operation of our website, we cannot identify you, and therefore, we cannot provide you with access to your personal data. Data is deleted in accordance with our retention policies stated above.
  8. Complaint to supervisory authority - You also have the right to file a complaint with the relevant supervisory authority (e.g. of your country or domicile) where we have not addressed your concerns.

### How does Reason Software update its privacy policy?

We may update this policy at any time by posting additions or modifications on this web page. If at any point we decide to use information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by email or via a prominent notice on our website.

### Contact us

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should first contact us by emailing to info@reasoncoresecurity.com

This privacy policy was last modified on May 29, 2018
